GERSON CABRERA

4107 Center St. Apt. D Tacoma, Wa, 98409

253.213.6795

ga_cabrera@icloud.com

Profile

Driven individual with extensive experience in customer service and in leadership roles. Efficient in a fast-paced setting, well-built interpersonal skills, strong written and oral communication in English and fluent in Spanish. Posses excellent comprehension and retention skills and thrive in a team environment. Experienced in running the floor while providing excellent communication with coworkers and managers alike.

Experience

Utility, International Paper; Olympia, Wa - July, 2018-Present

Produce quality products that are up to company superior standards, with little room for error. Practice and promote safety in the work environment, including learning safety protocol for individual machines. Maintain material organization and overall cleanliness. Flexible with shifts and positions, including mandatory overtime or day-of schedule changes.

Shift Supervisor, Starbucks, Tacoma, Wa - June, 2017 - March, 2018

Organize and brief partners on plays from Starbucks Playbook. Execute plays best suited for efficient drive-through times and lobby traffic while ensuring that Starbuck's 'North Star' agenda is put into play towards customers and partners. Create a positive environment for team members and customers. Ensure partners understand their responsibilities. Monitor floor in order to assess and address partner and customer needs. Provide updates and feedback to manager on general floor performance.

Barista, Starbucks, Tacoma, Wa - September, 2015 - June, 2017

Perform several Starbucks positions while providing excellent customer service; brewing and handcrafting beverages per instructions, ensuring that each drink conforms to the Starbucks standard; making sure any complaints are entertained in a positive manner with the North Star agenda always in mind.

Accomplishments

Working at Tacoma Place Starbucks, busiest lobby/drive-through store in our region; Barista Trainer certified; Verismo V Sales Lead during 2016 holiday season, selling over 30 Verismos in our store.

Education

Tacoma Community College – Computer Science, 1 year Graham Kapowsin High School - 2013

Skills

Bilingual, strong work ethic, leadership skills, positive attitude, communication skills, planning and organizing, tech-savvy, and excellent customer service skills.

References

Breanna Singleton, Barista, Starbucks | 253.302.0080 Bianca Garcia, Shift Supervisor, Starbucks | 253.590.9556 Alex Whitfield, Manager, Starbucks | 404.528.5157 Andrew Mamerto, Manager, Starbucks | 253.267.9420